Guide to the Peter Salovey, President of Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the president, 2012-2018; Accession 2019-A-0015
  - Administration
    - President
      - Speeches
        - Jiang Xixian Meeting at Shanghai Tiatung University, 2014-2015 (Box 6, Folder 7)
        - Staff Appreciation Day, 2014 June 9 (Box 6, Folder 8)
        - Staff Engagement Strategy, 2014 August 27 (Box 6, Folder 9)
        - Sterling Fellows Dinner, 2014 May 2 (Box 6, Folder 10)
        - Sterling Library Naïve Dedication, 2014-2015 (Box 6, Folder 11)
        - Town Hall, 2013 January 29 (Box 6, Folder 12)
        - Unite for Sight Conference - Global Health and Innovation, 2015 March 28 (Box 6, Folder 13)
        - United States - India Partnership Summit, 2014 Ocotber 1 (Box 6, Folder 14)
        - Unite Way Event, 2014 April 22 (Box 6, Folder 15)
        - Unite Way Leaderhip Reception, 2014 October 22 (Box 6, Folder 16)
        - University Development Council Remarks, 2013 February 27 (Box 6, Folder 17)
        - Veteran's Day Ceremony, 2014 November 11 (Box 6, Folder 18)
        - Jim Vlock Building Open House, 2013 September 30 (Box 6, Folder 19)
        - Vroom Festschrift Opening Remarks, 2013 June 7 (Box 6, Folder 20)
        - Waseda University Y-VISP Ceremony and Reception, 2013 April 25 (Box 6, Folder 21)
        - Washington DC Alumni Parents and Friends Event, 2013 April 20 (Box 6, Folder 22)
        - Windham Campbell Prize, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 23)
        - Windham Campbell Prize, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 24)
        - Windham Campbell Prize, 2015 February 24 (Box 6, Folder 25)
        - Women in Physics APS Conference for Undergraduate Women in Physics, 2015 January 16 (Box 6, Folder 26)
        - World Fellows Closing Ceremony, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 27)
        - Yale Alumni Fund, 2013 February 12 (Box 6, Folder 28)
        - Yale and Entreprenurship, 2014-2015 (Box 6, Folder 29)
        - Yale and New Haven, 2014 July 15 (Box 6, Folder 30)
        - Yale and the American Dream, 2013 August 24 (Box 6, Folder 31)
        - Yale Climate and Energy Institute, 2013 July 10 (Box 6, Folder 32)
        - Yale Club of Singapore, 2013 September 24 (Box 6, Folder 33)
        - Yale Development Council, 2014 October 23 (Box 6, Folder 34)
        - Yale Entrepreneurs at Goodwin Procter, 2014 April 1 (Box 6, Folder 35)
        - Yale Gale Forum, 2014 November 12 (Box 6, Folder 36)
        - Yale Leadership Center in Beijing, 2014 April 30 (Box 6, Folder 37)
        - Yale Medal Dinner, 2013 November 21 (Box 6, Folder 38)
        - Yale Medal Dinner, 2014 November 14 (Box 6, Folder 39)
        - Yale Program for the Study of Antisemitism Luncheon, 2014 September 22 (Box 6, Folder 40)
        - Yale Sports Federation, 2013 September 20 (Box 6, Folder 41)
        - Yale Sustainable Food Project, 2014 March 28 (Box 6, Folder 42)
        - Yale University Art Gallery Conference, 2014 May 9 (Box 6, Folder 43)
        - Yale Women Conference, 2013 April 20 (Box 6, Folder 44)
        - Yale-AGB Leadership Summit, 2014 January 14 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Provost Announcements, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Provost Associate Provost Antony Notes, 2014 July 7 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Provost "Big Issues" Notes, 2013 January 28 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Provost Correspondence Regrets, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Provost Correspondence Thank Yous, 2012-2013 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Provost Goals and Priorities, 2013-2014 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Provost Goals and Priorities, 2014-2015 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Provost Meeting, 2013 July 29 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Provost Peabody Funds, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Provost and Development Breakfast, 2013 February 6 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Provost and Development Meeting, 2014 January 8 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Provost and Development Meeting, 2014 March 5 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Provost and Development Meeting, 2014 November 12 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Provost and President Meeting, 2014 October 14 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Secretary Announcement, 2014-2015 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Deputy Secretary Appointment Correspondence, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Secretary Goals and Priorities, 2014-2015 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Secretary Position Structure, 2014-2015 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Secretary and Vice President for Student Life Goals and Priorities, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Secretary and Vice President for Student Life Goals and Priorities, 2014- 2015 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Secrearty and Vice President for Student Life Howard Announcement, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Vice President for Alumni Affairs and Development
    - O'Neill Announcement, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Annual Report of Giving to Yale - taping, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Donor Letter, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Donors Moulay Hicham Ben Abdellah, 2014-2015 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Donors
      - Ambani, Isha, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Bam, Foster, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Barry, Thomas, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 73)
      - Bass, Edward, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 74)
      - Bass, Robert, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 75)
      - Bass, Sid, 2014-2015 (Box 6, Folder 76)
      - Beinecke, William, 2013-2014 (Box 6, Folder 77)
      - Beinecke, William, 2014-2015 (Box 6, Folder 78)
      - Bekenstein, Josh, 2013-2014 (Box 6, Folder 79)
      - Bewkes, Jeff, 2014-2015 (Box 6, Folder 80)
      - Blavatnik, Len, 2013 (Box 6, Folder 81)
      - Blue Letters and lists January (folder 1 of 2), 2015 (Box 6, Folder 82)
      - Blue Letters and lists January (folder 2 of 2), 2015 (Box 6, Folder 83)
      - Blue Letters and Lists February, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 84)
      - Blue Letters and Lists March, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 85)
      - Bluse Letters and Lists April, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 86)
      - Blue Letters and lists May, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 87)
      - Blue Letters and Lists June, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 88)
      - Blue Letters and Lists July (folder 1 of 2), 2015 (Box 6, Folder 89)
      - Blue Letters and Lists July (folder 2 of 2), 2015 (Box 6, Folder 90)
      - Blue Letters and Lists August, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 91)
      - Blue Letters and Lists September, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 92)
      - Blue Letters and Lists October, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 93)
      - Blue Letters and Lists November, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 94)
      - Blue Letters and Lists December, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 95)
      - Blum, Irving and Jackie, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Botin, Emilio, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Brady, Nick, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Brady, Nick, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Breakstone, Noah, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Sterling, Mr. and Mrs., 2015 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Brown, Martin, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Bumett, Charles III, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Mr. Butt - Proposal, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Calabrese, Guido, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Cann, Ross, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Chanos, James, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Chapman, Lise, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Chomnalez, Franco and Herrera, Maria, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Chung, Bo, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Collins, Tim, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Conine, Jeffrey, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Conte, Jean-Pierre, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Cooper, Ethelbert, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Corrafiell, John, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Crosby, John, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Cullman, Edgar, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - Cullman, Edgar, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - Don Cummings, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - Cutler, Alexander, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - Cutler, Sandy, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - Dayton, Mr. and Mrs. Bruce, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - Dayton, Robert, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 28)
      - Dietz, Richard, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 29)
      - DeToro, Fran, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 30)
      - deVeer, Robert III, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 31)
      - John Dewey Estate, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 32)
      - Dilenschneider, 2013-2014 (Box 7, Folder 33)
      - Dilenschneider, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 34)
      - Donnelley, Strachan, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 35)
      - Doran, Robert, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - Dow, Mr. and Mrs. Robert, undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - Duncan, A. Baker, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 38)
      - Ellis, Charles, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 39)
      - Ellis, Douglas and Bing, Mary, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 40)
      - Fischer, David, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 41)
      - Fisher, Everett, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 42)
      - Ford, William, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 43)
      - Florida followup letters from MacMillan and Bologh Dinners, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 44)
      - Fortunoff, David, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 45)
      - Foster Presentation and Dinner, 2014 January 9 (Box 7, Folder 46)
      - Frank, Frederick, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 47)
      - Frank, Frederick and Tanner, Mary, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 48)
      - Franke, Mr. and Mrs. Richard, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 49)
      - Richard Franke Essay, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 50)
      - Freidheim, Stephen, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 51)
      - Friedman, Mikhail, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 52)
      - Friedlander, Jesse, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 53)
      - Furth, John, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 54)
      - Gaddis Dinner, 2014 January 30 (Box 7, Folder 55)
      - Gallogly, Mark, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 56)
      - Gates, Mimi, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 57)
      - Gilder, Richard, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 58)
      - Gilder, Richard and Chiles, Lois, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 59)
      - Gimbel, Louis III, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 60)
      - Glick, Adam, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 61)
      - Goldfarb, Robert, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 62)
      - Goldman, Jane, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 63)
      - Goldman, Robert, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 64)
      - Goodyear, Charles and Elizabeth, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 65)
      - Goodyear, Chip, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 66)
      - Goodyear Dinner, 2014 January 14 (Box 7, Folder 67)
      - Goodyear Dinner, 2015 January 19 (Box 7, Folder 68)
      - Gordon, W. Bing, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 69)
      - Grace, Joel, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 70)
      - Green, Holcombe, Jr., 2015 (Box 7, Folder 71)
      - Greenberg, Glenn and Linda, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 72)
      - Greenberg, Joseph and Claire, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 73)
      - Greenberg, Maurice, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Greenberg, Maurice, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 75)
      - Gruber, Peter, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 76)
      - Haas, Robert, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Hamp, Sheila, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - Harrington, Hadley, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Halpern, Abel and Helen, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 80)
      - Harrick, Stephen, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - Harrison, Mr. and Mrs. William, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 82)
      - Andrew Hauptman Notes, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 83)
      - Hauptman, Ellen and Andrew, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 84)
      - Hecht, Menachem, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 85)
      - Heinz Family, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 86)
      - Heinz, Teresa, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 87)
      - Hendel, Ruth, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 88)
      - Hendel, Mr. and Mrs. Stephen, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 89)
      - Hendel, Mr. and Mrs. Stephen, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 90)
      - Heyman, Ronnie, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 91)
      - Hickey, Stephen, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 92)
      - Hill, Calvin and Janet, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 93)
      - Hirschler, Charles, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 94)
      - Horchow, Roger, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 95)
      - Hume, George, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 96)
      - Hyde, Mrs. Joseph, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 97)
      - Iseman, Fred, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 98)
      - Jaffe, Thomas, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 99)
      - Irving Jensen Notes, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 100)
      - Irving Jensen Notes, 2015 March 3 (Box 7, Folder 101)
      - Jensen, Irving, Jr., 2015 (Box 7, Folder 102)
      - Johnson, Charles, 2013-2014 (Box 7, Folder 103)
      - Charlie Johnson Gift Responses, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 104)
      - Johnson, Charles, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 105)
      - Johnson, Mr. and Mrs. Gregory, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 106)
      - Jones, Daniel, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 107)
      - Jones, Mr. and Mrs. David, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 108)
      - Jones, David, Jr., 2015 (Box 7, Folder 109)
      - Jones, David, Jr. and Wheeler, Mary, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 110)
      - Jones, Timothy and Cardelus, Anne, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 111)
      - Juhn, Chinhui, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 112)
      - Kaczmarek, Jane, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 113)
      - Kamel, Saleh, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 114)
      - Kempner, Thomas, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 115)
      - Kennard, William, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 116)
      - Kenney, Jerome, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 117)
      - Kern, Mr. and Mrs. Arthur, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 118)
      - Kim, Maggie, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 119)
      - Kim, Mi-Hyung, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 120)
      - Klein, Mrs. Jonathan, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 121)
      - Kline, Scott, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 122)
      - Knobloch, Carla, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 123)
      - Kochar, Chanda and Deepak, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 124)
      - Koerner, Joseph, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 125)
      - Kohler, Herbert, Jr., 2015 (Box 7, Folder 126)
      - Kroon, Richard, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 127)
      - Krumholz, Regina, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 128)
      - Kumble, Steven, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 129)
      - Kutman, Mehmet, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 130)
      - Lampert, Edward, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 131)
      - Lawrence, James, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 132)
      - Lawrence, James and Mary, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 133)
      - Lee, William, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 134)
      - Marwell, Tracy Leeds and Evan, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 135)
      - Leigh, Abby, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 136)
      - Leigh, Mitch, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 137)
      - Leitner, James, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 138)
      - Levin, Mr. and Mrs. Richard, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 139)
      - Lighten, William, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 140)
      - Livingston, Catherine, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 141)
      - Loria, Jeffrey, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 142)
      - Loria, Jeffrey, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 143)
      - Loring, Mr. And Mrs. Ian, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 144)
      - Loucks, Vernon, Jr., 2015 (Box 7, Folder 145)
      - Lovett, Anne and Woodsum, Stephen, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 146)
      - Lubow, Oscar, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 147)
      - Luikart, James, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 148)
      - Lynch, Phillip, 2012-2013 (Box 7, Folder 149)
      - Lykouretzos, John, 2012 (Box 7, Folder 150)
      - Lyons, William, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 151)
      - MacMillan, Mr. and Mrs. Whitney, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 152)
      - Magliocco, Antonio, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 153)
      - Magliocco, Joseph, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 154)
      - Malone, John, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 155)
      - Marren, Lynda and John, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 156)
      - Marshall, Elaine, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 157)
      - Marks, Leonard, Jr., 2015 (Box 7, Folder 158)
      - Masters, Diana, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 159)
      - McCance, Henry, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 160)
      - McCullough, David, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 161)
      - McCullough, Cate, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 162)
      - McNamee, Roger, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 163)
      - McNay, Joseph, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 164)
      - Mele, Joseph, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 165)
      - Mele, Katherine and Joseph, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 166)
      - Messinger, William, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 167)
      - Meyer, Roslyn and Jerome, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 168)
      - Miller, Brian, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 169)
      - Millson, Rory, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 170)
      - Mittal, Rajan, 2014-2015 (Box 7, Folder 171)
      - Mobley, Kurt, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 172)
      - Moran, Garrett and Mary, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 173)
      - Moran, Garrett and Mary, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 174)
      - Morse, Mr. and Mrs. Robert, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 175)
      - Moses, Jack, 2014 (Box 7, Folder 176)
      - Muir, Pauli, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 177)
      - Mullen, Donald, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 178)
      - Munroe, Alexandra, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 179)
      - Nedungadi, Ajit and Aliya, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Neville, Charles, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Newhouse, Steven, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Newman, Mr. and Mrs. Howard, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Ng, Robert, 2012-2013 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Nolen, Christian, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Nolan, Eliot and Bradley, Timothy, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Nolen, Mr. and Mrs. Malcolm, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Nolen, Wilson, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Nooyi, Indra, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Ottaway, James, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Pepper, John, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Petrello, Anthony, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Phelps, Richard, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Poorvu Family, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Prtizker, Mr. and Mrs. John, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Pritzker, Karen, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Pritzker, Lisa, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Ramakrishnan, Guru, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Rausing, Lisbeth, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Redleaf, Mr. and Mrs. Andrew, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - Reeves, William, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Rice, Eve, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - Rice, Eve and Mattison, Tim, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 24)
      - Roberts, Brian, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 25)
      - Rose, Daniel, 2012-2013 (Box 8, Folder 26)
      - Rose, Daniel, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - Rose, Daniel, 2014-2015 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      - Daniel and Joanne Rose - Judaica Collections, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 29)
      - Rosenkranz, Robert and Munroe, Alexandra, 2013-2014 (Box 8, Folder 30)
      - Rose, Deborah, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 31)
      - Rose, Deborah and Rose, Sarah Visit, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      - Rose, Sandra, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 33)
      - Rosenkranz, Robert, 2014-2015 (Box 8, Folder 34)
      - Ross, Clifford, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 35)
      - Ryan, David, 2012-2013 (Box 8, Folder 36)
      - Saiontz, Leslie, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 37)
      - Salovey, Dr. and Mrs. Ronald, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 38)
      - Samson, David, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 39)
      - Schacht, Henry, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 40)
      - Schoen, Scott, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - Schusterman, Stacy and Dow, Steven, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - Schwab, Klaus, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 43)
      - Schwarzman, Stephen, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 44)
      - Schwarzman, Stephen, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 45)
      - Schwarzman, Stephen, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 46)
      - Scurci, John, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 47)
      - Segel, David, 2012-2013 (Box 8, Folder 48)
      - Sekoff, Roy, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 49)
      - Ivan Selin Notes, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 50)
      - Semler, Tracy, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 51)
      - Shaw, David and Beth, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 52)
      - Shen, Neil, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 53)
      - Shen, Theodore, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 54)
      - Shing, Li Ka and Chan, Solina, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 55)
      - Shelfer, Andrei and Zimmerman, Nancy, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 56)
      - Shorenstein, Mr. and Mrs. Douglas, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 57)
      - Singer, David, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 58)
      - Slaughter, William, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 59)
      - Smilow, Joel, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 60)
      - Smilow, Joel, 2013-2015 (Box 8, Folder 61)
      - Smilow, Joel, 2014-2015 (Box 8, Folder 62)
      - Smith, Fredrick, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 63)
      - Solomon, Andrew, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 64)
      - Sololoff, Mr. and Mrs. Jonathan, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 65)
      - Soros, Robert, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 66)
      - Stemerman, David, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 67)
      - Stoeckel Estate, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 68)
      - Strickler, Elizabeth and Gallogly, March, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 69)
      - Sunshine, Gabriel and Acuna, Geraldine, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 70)
      - Sze, David and Donoghue, Catherine, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 71)
      - Thomas, Mr. and Mrs. David, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 72)
      - Thorne, Oakleigh II, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 73)
      - Tisch, Jonathan, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 74)
      - Tisdale, Andrew and Nelson, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 75)
      - Tsai, Joe, 2012-2013 (Box 8, Folder 76)
      - Tsai, Joe, 2014-2015 (Box 8, Folder 77)
      - Tsukanora, Igor and Natasha, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 78)
      - Tung, C.H., 2014 (Box 8, Folder 79)
      - Tyler, James, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 80)
      - Unterberg, Kara, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 81)
      - van Agtmael, Antoine, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 82)
      - Vekelsberg, Viktor, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 83)
      - Vosburgh, Peter, 2014-2015 (Box 8, Folder 84)
      - Wang, Anthony, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 85)
      - Warner, Douglas III, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 86)
      - Warner, Sandy, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 87)
      - Weinstein, Tali, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 88)
      - Wells, Damon, 2014-2015 (Box 8, Folder 89)
      - Weyerhaeuser, Frederick, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 90)
      - Weymouth, Lally, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 91)
      - Whitestone, Dorsey, 2014-2015 (Box 8, Folder 92)
      - Whitestone, Randall, 2014-2015 (Box 8, Folder 93)
      - Wiley, Tom, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 94)
      - Wilson, Wallace, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 95)
      - David Windham Estate, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 96)
      - Wurtele, Mr. and Mrs. Angus, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 97)
      - Yang, James, 2012-2013 (Box 8, Folder 98)
      - Xin, Zhang, 2014-2105 (Box 8, Folder 99)
      - Xu, Xiaoping, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 100)
      - Zaleske, David, 2012-2013 (Box 8, Folder 101)
      - Zaleske, David, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 102)
      - Zeff, Ron, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 103)
      - Lei Zhang Dinner, 2014 March 17 (Box 8, Folder 104)
      - Zuckerberg, Mark, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - Financial Growth Report, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - Gifts and Pledges, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - Goals and Priorities, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - Goals and Priorities, 2014-2015 (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - Naming, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 110)
    - Notes, 2013-2014 (Box 8, Folder 111)
    - Office of Development and Association of Yale Alumni Kickoff, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - O'Neill Meeting, 2013 August 23 (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - O'Neill Meeting, 2013 September 4 (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - O'Neill Meeting, 2014 May 27 (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - O'Neill Meeting, 2015 June 3 (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - Phone Calls, 2014-2015 (Box 8, Folder 117)
    - Provost and Development Meeting, 2013 September 4 (Box 8, Folder 118)
    - Top Prospect Meeting, 2013 September 19 (Box 8, Folder 119)
    - Travel Planning, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 120)
    - Vice President for Finance and Business Operations
    - King Announcement, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 121)
    - Auditing, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 122)
    - Budget, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 123)
    - Budget Book, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 124)
    - Budget Update, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 125)
    - Budget Updates, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 126)
    - Capital Budget, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 127)
    - Federal 2014-2015 Fiscal Operations Report (Box 8, Folder 128)
    - Application for 2016-2017 (Box 8, Folder 129)
    - Financial Results, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 130)
    - Goals and Objectives, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 131)
    - Grants and Contracts Quarterly Management Report, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 132)
    - King Meeting Notes, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - Operating and Capital Budget, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 134)
    - Pavlis Search, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 135)
    - University Services Cost, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 136)
    - Vice President for Finanace and Chief Financial Officer Murphy Announcement, 2015 (Box 8, Folder 137)
    - Vice President for Global and Strategic Initiatives Lorimer Blog Post, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 138)
    - Vice President for Global and Strategic Initiatives Lorimer Meeting Notes, 2013 (Box 8, Folder 139)
    - Vice President for Global and Strategic Initiatives Lorimer Retirement Announcement, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 140)
  - Affiliated Units
    - Afro-American Cultural Center Anniversary, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 141)
    - Afro-American Cultural Center Consultation, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 142)
    - Blavatnik Entrepreneurship Institute, 2014 (Box 8, Folder 143)